Guide to the Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera, 1840-2016 and undated RL.00580
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 1940 Campaign
  - Willkie, Wendell Lewis, 1940
    - White button with green text: My Friends But Not My Subjects, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-084)
    - mint colored button with blue text: Two Times is Enough For Any Man, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-085)
    - White button with text: Let's Swap Riders Not Horses, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-086)
    - White button with text :Willkie (blue) Not Royal But (red) Loyal (blue), 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-087)
    - White button with oxidation and text: Willkie for President, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-088)
    - White button with text: No More New Deal We Want Square Deal, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-089)
    - White button with red border and text: He Will [drawing of key], 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-090)
    - Red buttpn with text: Dictator? Not For Us, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-091)
    - White pin with red text: I Told You So It's Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-092)
    - Yellow button with green text: Willkie For President of CommonWealth and Southern, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-093)
    - Yellow button with green text: We Don't Throw Rotten Eggs, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-094)
    - White button with text: We Woman Want Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-095)
    - White button with image of elephant stabbing a donkey and text: The Last Act, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-096)
    - White button with image of brown hat and text: East Side, West Side wants Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-097)
    - White button with blue text: 6,000,000 Piglets Squal "Hank Wallace's Raw Deal!", 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-098)
    - Red button with white border, image of elephant, and text: Life Beings in 40, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-099)
    - Faded white button with blue text: "My Day" When I Vote For Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-100)
    - White button with Text: No New Deal We Want A Square Deal, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-101)
    - Button with stars and stripes design around the border, portrait of Willkie and banner with elephant pin, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-102)
    - Blue button with text: Had Enough?, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-103)
    - Grey Button with burgandy text: Vagabonds, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-104)
    - White button with blue text: Willkie or Bust, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-105)
    - White button with stars and stripes banner and portrait of Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-106)
    - White button with blue text: There is No Indispensable Man, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-107)
    - Red, White and Blue button with tricolor banner and text: Willkie and Mcnary, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-108)
    - Red, White and Blue button with text: We the People need Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-109)
    - White button in the shape of a plaque or shield with portrait of Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-110)
    - White button with red border and blue text: We Want Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-111)
    - Gilded Elephant Pin (small), 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-112)
    - Small amber-like button with portrait of Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-113)
    - Pin in the shape of a key with American flag design and text: Willkie, McNary, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-114)
    - White button with text: Joe and Me for Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-115)
    - Pin with text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-116)
    - Red pin with beige border and text: Vote Republic: Willkie and McNary, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-117)
    - Button in the shape of a state (???) with black and white portrait of Wendell, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-118)
    - Pin with clock design and text: Time to Elect Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-119)
    - Pin with license plate design and text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-120)
    - Silver Pin in the shape of a key with text: Will-Key, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-121)
    - Circle Pin with red, white, and blue color scheme and text: Watch Willkie Win, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-122)
    - White button with red and blue text: Member Willkie Club, 1940 (Box 20, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-123)
    - Button with text: For Willkie President, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-124)
    - Button in the shape of shield with portrait of Willkie (b&w), 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-125)
    - Blue pin with text: Go Vote for Republican and image of Elephant, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-126)
    - Cream colored pin with image of American flag in shield and text: Willkie McNary, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-127)
    - Blue pin with text: Go Vote for Republican, and image of elephant, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-128)
    - Pin in the shape of state and black and white portrait of Willkie, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-129)
    - Blue and Gold Pin with text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-130)
    - Blue and orange pin with text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-131)
    - Blue and Silver Pin with text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-132)
    - Red, Blue, and Silver pin with text: Willkie, 1940 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-WLW1940-133)
    - Metal sign (for car license plate): We Want Willkie, 1940 (Box 13)
- 1944 Campaign
  - Dewey, Thomas Edmund, 1944
    - Speeches, pamphlets, 1944 (Box 13)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Dewey Bricker, 1944 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED1944-001)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Dewey and Bricker, 1944 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED1944-002)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Dewey Bricker, 1944 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED1944-003)
    - Pin red white and blue, stars, words: Dewey Bricker, 1944 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED1944-004)
    - Pin white with elephant, words: Dewey-Bricker N.Y. Young Republicans, 1944 (Box 25, Item RL-00580-TED1944-005)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1944
    - Democratic National Convention speeches, campaign literature, 1944 (Box 13)
    - Liberal Party of New York materials, 1944 (Box 13)
    - Pin with red border, attached ribbon, printed photograph of Roosevelt, and text: God Bless America, Roosevelt 1944-1948 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1944-001)
    - Pin with red border, printed photograph of Roosevelt, with text: We are going to win this war and win that peace that follows, 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1944-002)
    - Pen sepia tone with printed photograph of Roosevelt and text: Roosevelt-Truman, 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1944-003)
    - Pin with red and blue border with text: Roosevelt - Truman Save America, 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1944-004)
    - Pin with red and blue border with text: Roosevelt - Truman Save America, 1944 (Box 30, Item RL-00580-FDR1944-005)
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1944
    - Socialist Party Platform, 1944 (Box 13)
- 1948 Campaign
  - Dewey, Thomas Edmund, 1948
    - Button with printed photographs of Dewey and Warren with text: Dewey Warren, 1948 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-TED1948-001)
    - Pin with elephant and text: Dewey Warren, 1948 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-TED1948-002)
    - Republican Party factbook, 1948 (Box 13)
  - Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1948
    - Socialist Party Platform, 1948 (Box 13)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1948
    - Button with text: Students for Truman, 1948 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-HST1948-001)
    - Button with text: Don't Tarry Vote Harry, 1948 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-HST1948-002)
    - Litho tab with text: Truman, 1948 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-HST1948-003)
      RL-00580-HST1948-003 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 004
    - Litho tab with text: Truman, 1948 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-HST1948-004)
      RL-00580-HST1948-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 003
    - Democratic Party campaign literature, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Democratic National Convention materials, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Democratic Party Publicity Committee literature, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Democratic Digest newsletter, 1948 July-November (Box 13)
    - Democratic Party Women's Division literature, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Photocopied newspaper clipping: Dewey Defeats Truman, 1948 (Box 17)
  - Wallace, Henry, 1948
    - Progressive Party fact sheets, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Brooklyn Wallace-For-President materials, canvassing directions, 1948 (Box 13)
    - New Party/Progressive Party convention materials, founding platforms, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Flyers/leaflets, 1948 (Box 13)
  - Watson, Claude, 1948
    - Prohibitionist Party campaign literature, 1948 (Box 13)
- 1952 Campaign
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David, 1952
    - Organizing manual, campaign literature, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Citizens for Eisenhower press releases and newsletters, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Clippings and editorials, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Pamphlets, circulars, campaign speech, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Republican primary laws, policies for the Republican National Convention, 1952 (Box 13)
    - North Carolina/South Carolina anti-Stevenson pamphlets and literature, 1952 (Box 13)
    - North Carolina/South Carolina campaign literature; general campaign literature; clippings, 1952 (Box 17)
    - Newspaper advertisement mockups, 1952 (Box 17)
  - Harriman, William Averell, 1952
    - Button with text: Harriman, 1952 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-WAH1952-001)
      RL-00580-WAH1952-001 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002
    - Button with text: Harriman, 1952 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-WAH1952-002)
      RL-00580-WAH1952-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 001
    - Poster and pamphlet, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Bumper stickers: Harriman, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Hoopes, Darlington, 1952
    - Button with text: Vote Socialist Party, 1952 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-DXH1952-001)
    - Socialist Party literature, platform, convention minutes, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Kefauver, Carey Estes, 1952
    - Campaign literature, Kefauver Beacon newsletters, pamphlets, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Kerr, Robert Samuel, 1952
    - Button with text: It's Kerr Yes Sir!, 1952 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-RSK1952-001)
    - Promotional literature for Democratic nomination, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Pogo, 1952
    - Button with text: I go Pogo, 1952 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-POG1952-001)
    - Button with text: I go Pogo, 1952 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-POG1952-002)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Proehl, Fred, 1952
    - Greenback Party literature, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Russell, Richard Brevard, 1952
    - Pamphlets, correspondence, Georgia Democrats resolution, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Stassen, Harold, 1952
    - Campaign literature, Republican primary scorecard, pamphlets, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Newsletter: Presidential News (Stassen for President campaign literature), 1952 (Box 17)
  - Stevenson, Adlai Ewing, 1952
    - Bumper stickers: Forward with Stevenson, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Decal, North Carolina: Stevenson/Umstead, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Democratic Party platform, campaign handbook, publications, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Clippings, advertisements, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Speeches, July 21-September 14, 1952; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Speeches, September 15-October 25, 1952; 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Campaign broadsides, Anti-Eisenhower newsprint, 1952 (Box 17)
  - Taft, Robert A., 1952
    - Campaign literature, flyers, leaflets, 1952 (Box 14)
  - Warren, Earl, 1952
    - Campaign platform, 1952 (Box 14)
- 1956 Campaign
  - Byrd, Robert, 1956
    - Clippings, 1956 (Box 17)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight David, 1956
    - Button with printed photograph of Eisenhower and text: America Needs Dwight D. Eisenhower, Draft Ike in 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-001)
    - Pin with text: Ike 56, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-002)
    - Button with text: I Like Ike Even Better, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-003)
    - Button with text: I Still Like Ike, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-004)
      RL-00580-DDE1956-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 10
    - Button with text: I Still Like Ike, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-005)
      RL-00580-DDE1956-005 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 004, 10
    - Button with text: Ike in '56, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-006)
      RL-00580-DDE1956-006 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 007, 8
    - Button with text: Ike in '56, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-007)
      RL-00580-DDE1956-007 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 006, 8
    - Button with text: Ike in '56, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-008)
      RL-00580-DDE1956-008 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 006, 7
    - Button with text: Ike in 56, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-009)
    - Button with text: I Still Like Ike, 1956 (Box 2, Item RL-00580-DDE1956-010)
      RL-00580-DDE1956-010 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 004, 5
    - Republican Policy "Issues of 1956", 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Republican news and press releases, clippings, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Republican platform, pamphlets, voting laws, campaign literature, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Campaign memorabilia catalogs, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Bumper stickers: Re-elect Ike and Dick; Re-elect Eisenhower, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Republican National Committee mailings, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Press releases, campaign literature re: Nixon, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Newsletters: Straight from the Shoulder, Vote-Producing Ideas, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Campaign literature, talking points, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Newspaper clipping with quote from Eleanor Roosevelt re: human rights, 1956 (Box 17)
  - Stevenson, Adlai Ewing, 1956
    - Button with text: Stevenson Kefauver, 1956 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES1956-001)
    - Button with text: Stevenson and Kefauver, 1956 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES1956-002)
    - Litho tab with text: Stevenson Kefauver, 1956 (Box 4, Item RL-00580-AES1956-003)
    - Campaign literature, Democratic platform, 1956 (Box 14)
- 1960 Campaign
  - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald, 1960
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-001)
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-002)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 003, 4, 5, 6
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-003)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-003 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 4, 5, 6
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-004)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 3, 5, 6
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-005)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-005 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 3, 4, 6
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-006)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-006 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 3, 4, 5
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-007)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-007 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 008, 9, 10
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-008)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-008 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 007, 9, 10
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-009)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-009 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 007, 8, 10
    - Button with text: Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-010)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-010 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 007, 8, 9
    - Button with text: Kennedy Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-011)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-011 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0012
    - Button with text: Kennedy Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-012)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-012 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0011
    - Button with text: Kennedy Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-013)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-013 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0014
    - Button with text: Kennedy Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-014)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-014 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0013
    - Button with text: Let's Win!, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-015)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-015 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0016
    - Button with text: Let's Win!, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-016)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-016 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0015
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Our next President John F. Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-017)
    - Button with printed photographs of Kennedy and Johnson and text: America Needs Kennedy-Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-018)
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-019)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-019 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0020, 21, 22
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-020)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-020 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0019, 21, 22
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-021)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-021 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0019, 20, 22
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-022)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-022 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0019, 20, 21
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Students for Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-023)
    - Litho tab with text: Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-024)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-024 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0023, 24
    - Litho tab with text: Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-025)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-025 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0025, 26
    - Litho tab with text: Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-026)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-026 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0024, 25
    - Matchbook with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy for President / AFL CIO / Vote Democratic, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-027)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-027 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0028
    - Matchbook with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy for President / AFL CIO / Vote Democratic, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-028)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-028 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0027
    - Lenticular button with photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy for President He Will Win, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-029)
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-030)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-030 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0031
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-031)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-031 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0030
    - Button with text: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-032)
    - Button with text: Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-033)
    - Litho tab with text: Kennedy Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-034)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-034 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0035, 36
    - Litho tab with text: Kennedy Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-035)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-035 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0034, 36
    - Litho tab with text: Kennedy Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-036)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-036 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0034, 35
    - Litho tab with text: I'm working for Kennedy amp; Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-037)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-037 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0038
    - Litho tab with text: I'm working for Kennedy amp; Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-038)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-038 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0039
    - Tie clasp with lenticular photograph of Kennedy and text: The Man for the 60's, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-039)
    - Button with printed photograph of Kennedy and text: Prosperity for All with Kennedy, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-040)
    - Button with text: Elect Kennedy and Johnson, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-041)
    - Matchbook with printed photographs of Kennedy and Johnson, with text: Kennedy for President, Johnson for Vice President, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-042)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-042 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0043
    - Matchbook with printed photographs of Kennedy and Johnson, with text: Kennedy for President, Johnson for Vice President, 1960 (Box 5, Item RL-00580-JFK1960-043)
      RL-00580-JFK1960-043 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0042
    - Speeches and transcripts, 1960; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Campaign literature, Democratic platform, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Campaign kit, flyers, press releases, pamphlets, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Plastic banner: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Pro-Kennedy clippings, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Anti-Kennedy clippings, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Democratic Fact Sheet newsletters, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Students/Young Democrats literature, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Biographies of Kennedy, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Religious liberty/Catholicism literature, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Senior Citizens for Kennedy literature, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Bumper sticker: Vote Democratic, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Bumper stickers: Kennedy/Johnson, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Bumper stickers: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Plastic banner: Johnson for Vice President, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson materials, 1960 (Box 15)
    - Bumper sticker: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 17)
    - Plastic banners: Kennedy for President, 1960 (Box 17)
    - Posters, newspaper clippings, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Nixon, Richard Milhous, 1960
    - Button with text: Nixon and Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-001)
    - Button (yellow) with text: Nixon and Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-002)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-002 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 003, 4
    - Button (yellow) with text: Nixon and Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-003)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-003 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 4
    - Button (yellow) with text: Nixon and Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-004)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-004 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 002, 3
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-005)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-005 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 006, 7, 8
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-006)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-006 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 7, 8
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-007)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-007 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 6, 8
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-008)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-008 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 005, 6, 7
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-009)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-009 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 0010, 11, 12, 13, 14
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-010)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-010 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009, 11, 12, 13, 14
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-011)
      RL-00580-RMN1960-011 is a duplicate of the following RL IDs: 009, 10, 12, 13, 14
    - Button with text: Nixon Lodge, 1960 (Box 3, Item RL-00580-RMN1960-012)